<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Hugo Theme Stack Starter</title><link>https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Hugo Theme Stack Starter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Epic Quest for the Missing Dice</title><link>https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/blog/2025-02-28-the-epic-quest-for-the-missing-dice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/blog/2025-02-28-the-epic-quest-for-the-missing-dice/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="the-epic-quest-for-the-missing-dice">The Epic Quest for the Missing Dice
&lt;/h1>&lt;h2 id="chapter-1-the-disappearance">Chapter 1: The Disappearance
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>It was a dark and stormy night. Well, actually it was a perfectly pleasant Tuesday evening, but &amp;ldquo;dark and stormy&amp;rdquo; sounds more dramatic, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Our brave party had gathered around the sacred table (Dave&amp;rsquo;s dining room table with pizza stains), ready to embark on their first Draw Steel campaign. Character sheets were meticulously filled out. Snacks were abundant. The Game Master had spent three weeks crafting an adventure of unparalleled brilliance.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And then disaster struck.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Guys,&amp;rdquo; whispered Ellie, her face pale with horror, &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t find my lucky d20.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-2-the-search-begins">Chapter 2: The Search Begins
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The initial search was casual. A quick glance under the table. A peek between the couch cushions. But as minutes ticked by without the emerald green die appearing, panic began to set in.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;We can&amp;rsquo;t start without Ellie&amp;rsquo;s lucky die,&amp;rdquo; declared Sam. &amp;ldquo;Remember what happened last time?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Everyone shuddered, recalling the TPK incident of &amp;lsquo;23.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-3-desperate-measures">Chapter 3: Desperate Measures
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The party split up to cover more ground:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Dave crawled under the entertainment center, armed with only his phone flashlight&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mira investigated the kitchen, convinced the die had somehow rolled 40 feet across hardwood&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The GM sat quietly, watching the clock tick away precious gaming minutes&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-4-the-ancient-technique">Chapter 4: The Ancient Technique
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Okay, everyone stop moving,&amp;rdquo; said Dave, rising from the floor with the wisdom of countless lost dice searches. &amp;ldquo;We need to use the ancient technique.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t mean&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; gasped Mira.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Yes,&amp;rdquo; Dave nodded solemnly. &amp;ldquo;Everyone get down at eye-level with the floor and look for the shine.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-5-victory">Chapter 5: Victory!
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>It was Sam who spotted it. The faintest glimmer of green, nestled beneath the radiator, somehow balanced on its edge showing a perfect 20.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;IT&amp;rsquo;S AN OMEN!&amp;rdquo; cried Ellie, carefully extracting her precious die. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re going to absolutely crush this campaign!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The GM smiled knowingly. Little did they suspect that the real adventure was about to begin, as they prepared to draw steel for the very first time&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>This test post was created to verify that the Decap CMS is working correctly. If you&amp;rsquo;re seeing this on the live site, someone forgot to delete the test content. Oops!&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>